themesandco.com 2017-03-20

# Privacy Policy – Press Customizr

## Legal Notice

Press Customizr is a service offering of Press Customizr SARL, private company with a capital of € 30,000. The headquarters are located at 13 Boulevard Gambetta, 06000 Nice, FRANCE, and references in this document to “us,” “our,” and “we” refer to Press Customizr :

  * **Headquarter address :  13 Boulevard Gambetta, 06000 Nice, FRANCE**
  * **RCS registration number: 808 686 562**
  * **VAT number : FR70808686562**
  * **CNIL Declaration Number :  1852560 **( what is this ?  ***** )
  * **Publication director: Nicolas Guillaume**
  * **E-mail: contact[at]presscustomizr.com**
  * **Hosting:  PlanetHoster, 4416 Louis B Mayer, Laval, Quebec, H7P 0G1, Canada**

**© 2016 Press Customizr  SARL**

**Press Customizr  is a registered trademark.**

( ***** ) _The[Commission nationale de l’informatique et des libertés or CNIL](http://www.cnil.fr/english/the-cnil/ "CNIL website") (French pronunciation: [knil]; English: National Commission on Informatics and Liberty) is an independent French administrative regulatory body whose mission is to ensure that data privacy law is applied to the collection, storage, and use of personal data. Its existence was established by the French loi n° 78-17 on Information Technology, Data Files and Civil Liberty of 6 January 1978, and it is the national data protection authority for France. Source :  [CNILwikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Commission_nationale_de_l%27informatique_et_des_libert%C3%A9s "CNIL")_

_Since we collect private data (like emails) from our customers, Press Customizr must be registered to the CNIL to ensure that data privacy law is applied to the collection, storage, and use of your personal data._

## Privacy Policy

The Press Customizr (presscustomizr.com) Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

When you visit our website you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse the site.

### 1\. PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE

**Registration Information**  
You will provide us information about yourself, and your practices when you purchase Press Customizr products and services, register for forum support, or register for email newsletters and alerts.

**Email Information**  
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

### 2\. WEBSITE USE INFORMATION

Similar to other commercial websites, this site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how this site is used. European websites must follow the Commission’s guidelines on [privacy and data protection](http://ec.europa.eu/ipg/basics/legal/data_protection/index_en.htm) and inform users that cookies are not being used to gather information unnecessarily.

Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at this site, and the websites visited just before and just after our site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small technology or pieces of code to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.

#### HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to this website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in each such email.

#### WHAT ARE COOKIES?

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies that originate from their sites. We have no access or control over those cookies.

#### WHAT TYPE OF COOKIES ARE USED BY PRESSCUSTOMIZR.COM ?

The types of cookies used on our site can generally be put into one of the following categories: strictly necessary; analytics; functionality; advertising; and social media. You can find out more about each of the cookie categories in the table below.

Strictly Necessary Cookies | These cookies are essential to make our website work. They enable you to move around the site and use its features. Without these cookies, services that are necessary for you to be able to use our site such as accessing secure areas cannot be provided.  
---|---  
Analytics Cookies | These cookies collect information about how people are using our website, for example which pages are visited the most often, how people are moving from one link to another and if they get error messages from certain pages. These cookies don’t gather information that identifies you. All information these cookies collect is grouped together with information from other people’s use of our site on an anonymous basis. Overall, these cookies provide us with analytical information about how our site is performing and how we can improve it.  
Functionality Cookies | These cookies allow us to remember choices you make and tailor our site to provide enhanced features and content to you. For example, these cookies can be used to remember your user name, language choice or country selection, they can also be used to remember changes you’ve made to text size, font and other parts of pages that you can customise.  
Advertising Cookies | These cookies are used to deliver advertisements that are more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They remember that you have visited a website and this information may be shared with other organisations such as advertising partners. This means after you have been to our site you may see some advertisements about our services elsewhere on the Internet.  
Social Media Cookies | In order to enhance your internet experience and to make the sharing of content easier, some of the pages on our website may contain tools or applications that are linked to third party social media service providers such as Facebook, Twitter or Google+. Through these tools or applications the social media service provider may set its own cookies on your device. We do not control these cookies and you should check the social media service provider’s website for further details about how they use cookies.  
  
#### HOW DO WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM COOKIES?

As you use this website, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting this site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve this site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

#### SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

The information we collect is used to improve the content of this site and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes. That being said, your information could be shared under the following circumstances:

  * We use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, these third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with those business activities.
  * As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions.
  * We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.
  * If it becomes necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

#### NOTICE OF NEW SERVICES AND CHANGES

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to this website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in each such email.

#### HOW DO WE SECURE INFORMATION TRANSMISSIONS?

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Your payment informations will never been stored or known by Press Customizr since we use [Paypal](https://www.paypal.com/ "PayPal") and [Stripe](http://stripe.com/ "Stripe") as third party and highly secured payment gateways.

#### CERTAIN DISCLOSURES

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.

#### WHAT ABOUT OTHER WEBSITES LINKED TO THIS SITE?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our site. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our site to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including sites which have a link on our site, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

#### YOUR CONSENT

By using the website presscustomizr.com, the User is aware and agrees that Press Customizr and its team may collect personal and commercial information, which is information that identifies an individual or relates to an identifiable individual. This information is collected through fill-in forms. Some of the information requested is mandatory and necessary for processing the User’s requests. Information stored and collected is processed by the Press Customizr team and its commercial partners in order to provide the User the best service he/she requests under the best conditions.

Moreover, the User is aware and agrees that this personal data may be communicated to the Contributors as part of the claims process or for rectifications made on the website or to the software. They can also be communicated to commercial partners in order to carry out commercial processing.

The automatic processing of personal data has been declared to the Authority in charge of legal data protection in France. In respect of the law you can access, update, change and ask for the removal of your personal information at any time by writing to this address : contact@presscustomizr.com.

Finally, the User is aware and agrees that Press Customizr SARL can reveal and communicate your personal information in case of express order from a judge or a Court of Justice.

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.

#### APPLICABLE LAWS

We control and operate the site from our offices in France in accordance with the laws of France. We do not represent that materials on the Sites are appropriate or available for use in other locations. Persons who choose to access the Sites from other locations do so on their own initiative, and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.
